https://www.diabetesnet.com/privacy-policy/

Types & Causes of Diabetes
What Type Do I Have?
Eye Changes With Diabetes
Why Does Eye Damage Occur?
Special Suggestions for Handling Covid-19 with Diabetes
Covid-19 Ain’t the Common Seasonal Flu!
Correction Factor
The Bolus on Board (BOB or Unused Insulin)
High Blood Sugars
Severe Highs, Ketosis, and Ketoacidosis (DKA)
Carb Counting
What Are Carbs?
How Many Carbs Do You Need Each Day?
Diabetes in the Garden
Diabetes — Take A Hike!
Cyber Kitchen 51-60
Just In Case….
Cyber Kitchen 61-70
Climbing Stairs and Wild Salmon: A Common Bond?
World Diabetes Day & Pulses
Diabetes Doldrums
Tell Me What’s Going On?
Get Your Bones Ready to Go Outdoors
What’s Cooking?
Insulin Pumps
Why Use A Pump?
Tandem Announces t:slim X2 Pump
Tandem’s Project Odyssey May Change Upgrades from Hardware to Software
t:slim G4 Pump is here!
Continuous Glucose Monitors
Comparison of Current Continuous Glucose Monitors (CGMs)
Dexcom G6
Comparison of Current Continuous Glucose Monitors (CGMs)
Other Monitors – SenseWear
Diabetes Sentry (The Sleep Sentry Monitor)
Are Diabetes Advancements Worth The Cost?
Types & Causes of Diabetes
What Type Do I Have?
Eye Changes With Diabetes
Why Does Eye Damage Occur?
Special Suggestions for Handling Covid-19 with Diabetes
Covid-19 Ain’t the Common Seasonal Flu!
Correction Factor
The Bolus on Board (BOB or Unused Insulin)
High Blood Sugars
Severe Highs, Ketosis, and Ketoacidosis (DKA)
Carb Counting
What Are Carbs?
How Many Carbs Do You Need Each Day?
Diabetes in the Garden
Diabetes — Take A Hike!
Cyber Kitchen 51-60
Just In Case….
Cyber Kitchen 61-70
Climbing Stairs and Wild Salmon: A Common Bond?
World Diabetes Day & Pulses
Diabetes Doldrums
Tell Me What’s Going On?
Get Your Bones Ready to Go Outdoors
What’s Cooking?
Insulin Pumps
Why Use A Pump?
Tandem Announces t:slim X2 Pump
Tandem’s Project Odyssey May Change Upgrades from Hardware to Software
t:slim G4 Pump is here!
Continuous Glucose Monitors
Comparison of Current Continuous Glucose Monitors (CGMs)
Dexcom G6
Comparison of Current Continuous Glucose Monitors (CGMs)
Other Monitors – SenseWear
Diabetes Sentry (The Sleep Sentry Monitor)
Are Diabetes Advancements Worth The Cost?
A Great Instagrammer to follow
If you use our store, we collect your name, address, and email. Paypal handles payment information. We never directly receive your credit card numbers and have no way of accessing this information.
We use the Personal Information you submit or that we collect to operate, maintain, and provide you with the features and functionality of our online store. We use your information to provide you with customer service under our agreement. By providing us with your email address, you acknowledge we may use the email address to send you service-related notices, including any notices required by law, instead of communication by postal mail. You also acknowledge that we may send you notifications of activity on our store to the email address you give us, per any applicable privacy settings. We may use your email address to send you other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt-out or change your preferences in your account settings page. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or offers. You may not opt-out of Service-related e-mails.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
What is a cookie?
Cookies are small text files which are downloaded to and stored on your device when you visit a website. Cookies are widely used by website owners to provide you with a good experience while you browse, and also to provide information which can help us improve our website.
Our site uses cookies to:
make our site work
collect anonymous data on how users navigate our site, which helps us to improve it
allow you to share our content on social networks
help us provide relevant advertising to those who may be interested in it
We do not use cookies to:
collect any personally identifiable information
pass personal identifiable data to third parties
What cookies will we use and for what purposes?
We have split the cookies used on our site into four categories – strictly necessary cookies, functional cookies, performance cookies and advertising cookies. Each of these categories is explained below along with details of the specific cookies used, though within each category we may use additional or alternative cookies at any time. Please note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be performance cookies or advertising cookies.
A. Strictly Required Cookies These cookies are required for the website to run and cannot be switched off. Such a cookie is only set in response to actions made by you such as language, currency, login session, privacy preferences. You can set your browser to block these cookies, but our site may not work then.
B. Analytics and Statistics These cookies allow us to measure visitors’ traffic and see traffic sources by collecting information in data sets. They also help us understand which products and actions are more popular than others.
C. Marketing and Retargeting Our marketing and advertising partners usually set these cookies. They may be used by them to build a profile of your interest and later show you relevant ads. If you do not allow these cookies, you will not experience targeted ads for your interests.
D. Third-party cookies We use some third-party services or software on our website. If you go to a page on our website that contains this embedded content you may be sent cookies from these websites, for example, YouTube videos, Google maps, Facebook and Twitter. We do not control the setting of these cookies, so we suggest you check the third-party website for more information about their cookies and how to manage them.
Controlling the use of cookies
Most internet browsers automatically accept cookies unless you change your browser settings. If you wish to restrict, block or delete the cookies which are set by any websites, you can generally do this through your browser settings. These settings are usually found in the ‘options’ or ‘preferences’ menu of your internet browser. Please note however that if you set your internet browser preferences to block all cookies, you may not be able to access all or parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your internet browser settings to block cookies, our site will set cookies.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Third Party Analytics Services
Diabetes Services uses third party analytics services. See here for how Google uses data when you use our Service and how you may opt-out (www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).
This is what we don’t do with your data:
We are not sharing your personal data with any third parties
We are not processing your data via non-SSL connections
We are not reselling your data
We are not monetizing your data
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Following termination or deactivation of your account, we may retain your profile information and User Content for a commercially reasonable time for backup, archival, contract performance and enforcement, or audit purposes but for no longer than is necessary and only where the information is accurate and relevant for our use. Furthermore, we may retain and continue to use indefinitely all information (including User Content) contained in your communications to other Users or posted to public or semi-public areas of the Service after termination or deactivation of your User account.
Search for:
Advertisement
Mask now available in the store!
Time in Range: A New Standard?
What Type Do I Have?
Why Does Eye Damage Occur?
Covid-19 Ain’t the Common Seasonal Flu!
The Bolus on Board (BOB or Unused Insulin)
Severe Highs, Ketosis, and Ketoacidosis (DKA)
What Are Carbs?
How Many Carbs Do You Need Each Day?
Diabetes — Take A Hike!
Just In Case….
Climbing Stairs and Wild Salmon: A Common Bond?
World Diabetes Day & Pulses
Diabetes Doldrums
Tell Me What’s Going On?
Get Your Bones Ready to Go Outdoors
What’s Cooking?
Why Use A Pump?
Tandem’s Project Odyssey May Change Upgrades from Hardware to Software
t:slim G4 Pump is here!
Comparison of Current Continuous Glucose Monitors (CGMs)
Dexcom G6
Comparison of Current Continuous Glucose Monitors (CGMs)
Diabetes Sentry (The Sleep Sentry Monitor)
Are Diabetes Advancements Worth The Cost?
